365celebrations.com 2013-04-30

# Privacy

|   | 

Understand Yourself  

  * Man and Woman 
  * The Science of Awareness
  *  The Power of Mind
  * Find Yourself
  * Two-Dimensional Science 
  * Dive Into Life 
  * The Phenomenon of Emotions
  * Start From Physical Body  

Personal Success 

  * Become a Happy Personal Achiever
  * Self-Awareness as the Foundation  
\- action exercises 
  * Developing Personality  
\- personal beliefs  
\- set strategic goals  
\- develop positive attitude  
\- boost your creativity  
\- build self-confidence  
\- start acting 

  * Find Balance in Your Life 

Professional Success 

  * Become a Happy Professional Achiever
  * The Power of Leadership  
\- 15 leadership roles  
\- foundation of leadership  
- 26 leadership-management lessons
  * The Power of Knowledge  
\- cross-functional learning   
\- learn by doing   
\- manage failures   
\- become a strategic thinker
  * Creative Problem Solving  
\- unlock your creativity   
\- power of 80/20 rule  
- lateral thinking  
\- thinking outside the box   
-perfect brainstorming   
\- idea evaluation techniques  
\- six thinking hats
  * The Power of People Skills  
\- rules for long-term relationships   
\- effective communication  
\- face-to-face communication   
\- learn body language  
\- effective speaking and presentation
  * The Power of Intuition

|   
---  
  
|   
---  

**Privacy Policy**  

(Last updated November 01, 2011)

Oleg Moskvine ("the Author") cares about the privacy of each user of the Author's web site. The following provisions explain how the Author handles personal information.

This Privacy Policy consists of several principles to protect and manage your (the customer's) personal information. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that the Author does not own or control or to people that the Author does not employ or manage.

Identifying the Purpose of Personal Information: 

When you use this web site some basic information is collected. The web site collects, at time of your registration and your sign-on to the web site, certain "personal information" that you voluntarily give the Author (information that personally identifies you) such as your name, email address, home or work address, telephone number.

The Author's web sites may automatically receive and record basic general non personally-identifiable information from your browser including IP address, browser type, access times, and page you requested for the limited purposes to compile statistics to improve the Author's web sites and make your use of the Author's web sites efficient 

When you visit the Author's web sites, a cookie may be placed on your computer or the cookie may be read if you have visited the Author's web sites previously. The Author's web sites use cookies to allow to determine which products and services you use and the support you may need and to help detect and solve any problems you may have when using the Author's web sites. If you wish, you may set your browser to reject all cookies.

The Author uses information for the following general **Identified Purposes:**

To customize the advertising and content you see on the web pages, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services and to contact you on an opt-in basis about specials and new products.

Consent for Collection, Use or Disclosure 

The Author does not collect personal information without an individual's consent. 

The Author makes every reasonable effort to make sure that an individual understands how her or his personal information will be used. Registration for the the Author's web sites and the Author's services and products by a customer will constitute the customer's consent for the Author's web sites to collect, use and disclose personal information under this Privacy Policy. 

The Author will normally seek a customer's consent for any new uses and disclosures of the customer's personal information, either at the same time it collects the personal information or after it has been collected but before it is used or disclosed for a new purpose. An individual may withdraw such consent for collection, use and disclosure at any time, on prior written notice.

Limiting the Collecting, Using, Disclosing and Keeping Personal Information 

The Author limits its collection of personal information to only that information which is necessary for the Identified Purposes. The  Author's web sites do not knowingly collect personal information from children.

The Author will not sell, share or trade your personal information with others. The Author does not disclose individual personal information to others, except if required in the course of fulfilling the identified purpose for which it was collected.  

**Anti-Spam**

The Author's web sites are committed to permission-based (opted-in) email marketing practices.

The Author does not participate in spamming. Those who enter into business relationships with the Author (including, but not limited to, affiliates ) and choose to promote the  Author's  products or services, or the author's web sites affiliated products or services using spam will have their relationship with the Author immediately terminated. 

The Author respects the request of any individual asking to have his/her e-mail address opted-in and opted-out of the Author's database. As well, every e-mail sent by the Author provides an automated unsubscribe option at the bottom of each e-mail. All other unsubscribe requests can easily be processed by sending an e-mail, including the e-mail address you wish to remove.

Accuracy of Personal Information 

The Author will use reasonable efforts to keep customer personal information accurate for the Identified Purposes. Customers are responsible for informing the Author about changes to their personal information.

Security Safeguards 

The Author will use reasonable efforts to protect personal information against loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, misuse or modification, through security safeguards that depend on the level of sensitivity of the information. 

Access to Personal Information 

At the written request of individual the Author will tell him or her what personal information the Author has about the individual , what is being used for and to whom it has been disclosed.

**Questions.**  
Any questions and suggestions about the Author's handling of personal information should be directed to:

infosite@365celebrations.com 

**Notice of Change to the Privacy Policy**

The Author reserves the right to change and update this Policy from time to time. When it does, the Author will also revise the "last update" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. For changes to this policy,the Author will notify you by placing a notice on our web site home page.

Your continued use of the Author's web sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

**Copyright © Oleg Moskvine, 2010-2012. All Rights Reserved.**

|
